Guide to the The Inquiry Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Oversize Maps (Miscellaneous Printed Materials), 1856, 1868-1919
  - Africa
    - Photostats:
      - Map showing spread of Malaria throughout the world (Folder 34D)
      - Map of world centered on Africa showing the distribution of Trypanosoma (carrier of sleeping sickness) (Folder 34D)
  - Turkey
    - Photostats
      - Agricultural statistics (Folder 34A)
      - Political divisions of Arabia, 1917, 3 copies, I colored to show tribes (Folder 34A)
      - Arabia, etc. to accompany Westermann-Campell report on transportation (Folder 34A)
      - Turkey in Asia to accompany Westermann-Campbell report on transportation (Folder 34A)
      - Relation of Archdioceses in Greek Patriarchate of Constantinople to Vilayets (Asia Minor) (Folder 34A)
      - World (part) Spread of Islam (Folder 34A)
      - Base map, Anatolia & Armenia 1/2m colored to show density of population (Folder 34A)
      - Photostat of base map, as above (Folder 34A)
      - 4 copies, Railroads in Turkey, from Bull. Vol. XLVII, 1915 (Folder 34A)
      - 1 copy Distributions of Armenians in Turkish Armenia. From Bull. Vol. XLVII, 1915 (Folder 34A)
      - Hand-drawn & colored map, Turkey in Asia, showing races (Folder 34A)
      - Constantinople: Boundary lines - both proposed and existing (2 copies) (Folder 34A)
      - Constantinople: Relief map of same area in the above map (2 copies) (Folder 34A)
      - Albanian frontier, showing distributions of tribes (Folder 34A)
      - Balkan Exhibit R:7 (Folder 34A)
      - Greco-Bulgarian frontier, existing and proposed roads, railroads, water partings, etc. (Folder 34A)
      - Greek-Albania frontier, Greek claims, religious frontier, linguistic frontier, etc. (Folder 34A)
      - Macedonia (Folder 34A)
      - Southern Albania, line of Greek Occupation of 1915 (Folder 34A)
  - Balkans
    - Photostats
      - Rumania, Esquisse de la distribution des Charbons (Folder 34C)
      - Thrace, Dioces es Grecs, Divisions administratives Turques, ligne ethnographique de San Stephano (Folder 34C)
      - Greece - Annex II, Plan of ore districts (Folder 34C)
      - Fiume - Trade of... & adjacent regions (Folder 34C)
      - Balkans. Several maps showing agricultural statistics (Folder 34C)
      - Balkans. 4 sheets of G.S.G.S. map of Balkans, 1:250,000 showing racial statistics of Albania, Bulgaria, and Greece (Folder 34C)
      - Zupanic's map of Jugoslav territory (Folder 34C)
      - Railway Adriatico a Constantinople (Folder 34C)
      - Serbia - political divisions, exhibit 17 (Folder 34C)
      - Part of Danube administered by mixed Commission, Ex. Q4 (Folder 34C)
      - Neutral Albania, T8 (Folder 34C)
      - Albania, boundary proposed by Willis Monroe R 10 (Folder 34C)
      - Frontiers, Greece-Serbia-Bulgaria Maps 7 & 9 (Folder 34C)
      - Region around Salonica, ethnographic Map 5 (Folder 34C)
      - Balkans (Schurman - Ex. E-2) (Folder 34C)
      - Free Macedonia Map O (Folder 34C)
      - Ethnographic Map TI2 (Folder 34C)
      - Exhibit R2 Albania - Boundaries
      - Exhibit G Monroe (W.S.) Bulgaria, ethnographic frontier (Folder 34C)
      - Exhibit 23 Dr. Lupu's map showing his idea of West boundary of Rumania (Folder 34C)
      - Exhibit M White - Boundaries Balkans (Folder 34C)
      - Exhibit N Bourchier - Boundaries Balkans (Folder 34C)
      - 2 Base maps Balkans, 1:2,000,000 colored 1) showing regions in which there is no dominant race; 2) proposed boundaries (Folder 34C)
      - T I Cvijic, ethnographic Balkans (Folder 34C)
      - T II Balkans, conflicting ethnic claims (Folder 34C)
  - General Miscellaneous
    - Europa, Sprachen & Volkerkarte. Debes sheet 12c (Folder 34B)
      Enlarged photostat colored.
    - Hand colored Index to Base maps published of Europe. Base Johnston's Wall outline map of Europe. (Folder 34B)
    - Photostat positive of above, colored (Folder 34B)
    - 3 photostat negatives of List of Books from N.Y. Public Library (Shotwell) (Folder 34B)
    - Original drawing, No. 688 W. Haskins Holland, boundary changes (Folder 34B)
    - Siberian map from Pres. Barrows. photostats (Folder 34B)
  - The World
    - Outline map; original drawing, large & small sizes, Nos. 710 & 710 a. (Folder 35A)
    - Outline map, showing African Colonies, 692 (Folder 35A)
  - North America
    - Outline map of North America comparing Br. Honduras and Alaska Panhandle, 722. (Box 35C)
    - The Alaska Panhandle (drawing & photostat), 721. (Box 35C)
    - The Alaska Panhandle (just photostat), 678. (Box 35C)
  - Europe
    - A.G.S. base map, 1:3,000,000 (showing propositions), 679, 1919 January (Folder 35B)
    - A.G.S. base map, 1:6,000,000. Propositions, 679b, 1919 January (Folder 35B)
    - A.G.S. base map, 1:6,000,000, Propositions, 776b, 1919 March (Folder 35B)
    - A.G.S. base map, 1:6,000,000, Propositions, 679a, 1918 November (Folder 35B)
    - A.G.S. base map, 1:6,000,000, Propositions, 776c, 1919 April 2 (Folder 35B)
    - A.G.S. base map, 1:6,000,000, Propositions, 776a, 1919 March 31 (Folder 35B)
    - A.G.S. base map, 1:6,000,000, Propositions, 792, Undated (Folder 35B)
    - A.G.S. base map, 1:6,000,000, The Aspirations of January, 487 & 487b, 1919 January (Folder 35B)
    - A.G.S. base map, 1:6,000,000, Main boundary changes of Balkans & Central Europe added in colors, 758 (Folder 35B)
    - A.G.S. base map, 1:6,000,000, Population density, 563a (Folder 35B)
    - A.G.S. base map, 1:3,000,000 Part of map, covering Central Europe, marked to show boundary changes, 758a (Folder 35B)
    - Political Europe, end of February, 1919 (photostat), 723b (Folder 35B)
    - Propositions - March 1919 (photostat- 2 copies), 776a, 1919 March (Folder 35B)
    - Claims - March 1919 (photostat), 758, 1919 March (Folder 35B)
    - The Promises of 1916 (photostat), 757b (Folder 35B)
    - Waterways of Middle Europe (3 copies), 529 (Folder 35B)
    - Europe I/M - War Office, London. Sheets: (Folder 35B)
      - Sofiya, No. 682
      - Athenal, No. 683
      - Istambul, No. 681
      - Vienna & Krakau, No. 1652
      - Trieste & Roma, No. 781
      - Budapest, No. 781
      - Trieste, No. 781
      - Sofiya & Istanbul, No. 727
  - Austria-Hungary
    1) Quantities in thousands of tons 766
    2) Values in millions of crowns 765
    - A.G.S. base, 1/3M Trade of Fiume & adjacent regions, 775, 1910 (Folder 35D)
    - A.G.S. base, 1/3M (2 editions), 12a, 1910 (Folder 35D)
    - A.G.S. base, 1/3M Old Austria-Hungary, 57, 1914 (Folder 35D)
    - A.G.S. base, 1/2M Kreises, 506 (Folder 35D)
    - A.G.S. base, 1/M (2 sheets), 12 (Folder 35D)
    - A.G.S. base, 1/5M, 506a (Folder 35D)
    - A.G.S. base, 1/6M, 57a (Folder 35D)
    - Austria-Hungary (PI. from Atlas Universal), 1915 (Folder 35D)
    - Austria-Hungary 1:3,000,000, 564 (Folder 35D)
    - Austria-Hungary (base), 663 (Folder 35D)
    - Austria-Hungary (new divisions in red), 664 (Folder 35D)
    - Trade of Fiume, 1913 (Folder 35D)
    - Population engaged in production, 726 (Folder 35D)
    - Distribution of languages 1:2,000,000, 101a (Folder 35D)
    - 1/2M (showing proposed lines in Tyrol & Istria, London Pact Line, Masaryk Line, 610 (Folder 35D)
    - Drawing & Copy
      - Combined sheets, Europe 1/M British War Office Map, colored to show area of Hungarian speech, 612 (Folder 35D)
      - 2 untitled drawings, on linen. One unnumbered, other numbered, 493 (Folder 35D)
      - Territory taken from Rumania by Austria-Hungary & Bulgaria, acc. to Peace of Buckharest, 525, 1918 May (Folder 35D)
      - Map (photostat) showing Czecho-Slovak & Ruthenian areas, 699 (Folder 35D)
  - Danube River
    - The Danube of Treaty of Berlin (1878) and of London (1883) and of Paris (1856), 525 (Folder 35F)
    - Treaty before and of Paris, 525a (Folder 35F)
    - Danube between Braila and the Sea, by Sir Chas. Hartley, 1870-1871, 526 (Folder 35F)
    - Soulina arm with the cut-offs made from 1868-1902, 527 (Folder 35F)
    - Danube between Moldava and Turnu-Severin, 528 (Folder 35F)
  - Finland
    - A.G.S. base (part of map of Europe, 1:3,000,000), drawing and copy, 630 (Folder 35G)
    - Finland (drawing on linen, showing railways), Drawing and 2 copies, 536 (Folder 35G)
    - Finland, Esthonia and Lettonia. Linguistic boundary. (Folder 35G)
  - Germany
    - A.G.S. base, 1:6,000,000 (boundary changes added in color), 59a (Folder 35E)
    - A. G. S base, 1:3,000,000 (Treaty of London line added), 59 (Folder 35E)
    - A.G.S. base, 1:3,000,000 (boundaries & plebiscites, etc.), 784 (Folder 35E)
    - A.G.S. base, 1:3,000,000 (colored to show proposed boundaries, etc.), 704 (Folder 35E)
    - Germans in Germany and out. (photostat reduction of A.G.S. base. 1:6,000,000; colored), 1919 April 30 (Folder 35E)
    - What would be left of Germany?, 609a (Folder 35E)
    - Bevolkerung der Kreise, 1890 (photostat of western half of Germany), 716 (Folder 35E)
    - Allemagne (ouest & est) 1/M -Boundaries of Germany. (2 copies), 1919 (Folder 35E)
    - Territoire de la Sarre. S.G.S., 1:100,000, 1919 (Folder 35E)
    - Germany 1:1,500,00 G.S.G.S. 2758. (grades on 2 railways, routes Frankfurt a/M to Prague, added), 719 (Folder 35E)
    - Germany (outline map) (2 copies), 785 & 562 (Folder 35E)
    - Die Erzlagerstatten Oberschlesiens, by K. Flegel. (photostat & colored transparency), 755 (Folder 35E)
    - Ubersichtskarte der Bezitz-Verhaltnisse in Oberschlesischen Steinkohlenrevier…by R. Michael. (photostat - 2 copies), 756 (Folder 35E)
    - Cercle de Treves. Int. Sarre State. (photostat of original sketch) (Folder 35E)
    - (Sarre - mineral district. Photostat) 1:700,000, 605 (Folder 35E)
    - Germany 1:3,000,000 (photostat & drawing, outline, based on Adress Atlas sheet, 41-42), 488 (Folder 35E)
    - Karte der Wahlkreiseinteilung…1:1,500,000 (photostat), 717 (Folder 35E)
    - Germany in Kreise. (outline), 717 (Folder 35E)
    - Combined sheets, Europe I/M, War Office, London, covering Germany and adjacent, with proposed boundaries added in heavy lines, 609 (Folder 35E)
    - Brest-Litovsk boundary between Germany and Russia. 1:3,200,000 (on tracing linen), 496 (Folder 35E)
  - Alsace-Lorraine
    - Photostats
      - Maps and text from Richesses Minerales du Nordest (Professor Haskins) (Folder 35I)
      - Territorial changes and mineral resources density of population (Folder 35I)
      - Block diagram showing terrain of Lorraine and adjacent districts (Folder 35I)
        Showing topography and mineral basins.
      - Deep-drillings in the Oligocene Era rocks of the Upper Alsace (Folder 35I)
      - Miscellaneous photostat maps of Alsace-Lorraine (2) (Folder 35I)
  - Schlesvig-Holstein
    - Percent of Danish speech, 543 (Folder 35H)
      On tracing linen and colored copy on tracing paper.
    - (Outline map, railways, etc. MS), 684 (Folder 35H)
    - (Outline map, plebiscites, etc. MS on tracing paper and photostat), 789 (Folder 35H)
    - (Schlesvig, linguistic areas, etc. on tracing paper), 646a (Folder 35H)
    - Photostat of assembled sheets, Germany 1:100,000 (giving linguistic areas, etc.), 646a (Folder 35H)
  - Poland
    - A.G.S. base, Polish linguistic border line in Prussian Province added. H.Arctowski. 645, 1919 January 4 (Folder 35J)
    - A.G.S. base, (part of Europe 1/3,000,000) (drawing and copy), 624 (Folder 35J)
    - A.G.S. Base 1/2,000,000, 31a (Folder 35J)
    - (part of 1/6,000,000 map. Historical boundaries added) (Folder 35J)
    - A.G.S. Base 1:8,000,000 Poland and Lithuania, 32a (Folder 35J)
    - Pologne. (boundaries proposed, etc.) (Folder 35J)
    - Poland, 1/5,000,000 (photostat), 687 (Folder 35J)
    - Poland, Grand proprietes foncieres (Folder 35J)
      Photostat, colored.
    - Poland, Lithuania and W. Ukraine (linguistic boundaries), 657 (Folder 35J)
    - Poland, 687 (Folder 35J)
      On transparent paper- outline map with railways.
    - Poland, Proposed boundaries (Folder 35J)
      Colored photostat.
    - Poland, Cholm Region (No. 534) (Folder 35J)
  - Spitzbergen
    - Minerals (2 copies), 768 (Folder 35K)
    - Bear Island, 770 (Folder 35K)
  - Atlantic Ocean
    - 1:17,500,000 (outline) (Folder 35L)
  - Pacific Ocean
    - Map to illustrate partition of German possessions in Pacific at conclusion of the war (4 copies), 644 (Folder 35M)
  - Forests
    - A.G.S. map of the forests of Europe (Folder 35N)
    - A.G.S. map of the forests of Asia (Folder 35N)
    - A.G.S. map of the forests of North America (Folder 35N)
    - A.G.S. map of the forests of South America (Folder 35N)
    - A.G.S. map of the forests of Africa (Folder 35N)
    - A.G.S. map of the forests of Oceanica (Folder 35N)
    - Statistical Charts
      - Forest acreage of Allied, Enemy, and Neutral Nations (Folder 35N)
      - Forest acreage of Allied, Enemy, and Neutral Nations (broken down into temperate and tropical forests) (Folder 35N)
      - Actual and normal forest acreage per 100 inhabitants in Allied, Enemy, and Neutral Nations (Folder 35N)
      - Annual growth, production, consumption and net exports and imports of wood of Allied, Enemy, and Neutral Nations (Folder 35N)
  - The Balkans
    - A.G.S. base, 1:6,000,000, 61a (Folder 36D)
    - A.G.S. base, 1:4,000,000, 16a (Folder 36D)
    - A.G.S. base, 1:3,000,000 (outline), 505 (Folder 36D)
    - A.G.S. base, 1:3,000,000 (being part of Europe I/3M), 626 (Folder 36D)
    - A.G.S. base, Block Diagram (small edition) (Folder 36D)
    - Balkans, linguistic boundary (photostat reduction of 626), 655 (Folder 36D)
    - Balkans, rainfall (& photostat), 492 (Folder 36D)
    - Balkans, 574 (Folder 36D)
      On tracing linen, no legend given.
    - Balkans, Minerals of the Balkans (Folder 36D)
    - Balkans, Block diagram showing terrain of Balkan Peninsula (Folder 36D)
  - Albania
    - A.G.S. Block Diagram (small), 49a (Folder 36E)
    - Carte ethnographique de I'Albania, par N. Lako, 712 (Folder 36E)
      Present frontier & reasonable rectification added- Day; also photostat reduction, and tracing on linen.
    - Albania, proposed Serbian Protectorate (War Office base, I/M), 648 (Folder 36E)
  - Belgium
    - A.G.S. base, part of Europe 1:3,000,000 (and photostat reduction), 623 (Folder 36F)
    - Belgian frontiers (historical; photostat), 709 (Folder 36F)
    - Belgium, 665 (Folder 36F)
      Possible strategic rectification of Prussian frontier.
    - La Belgique en 1786, 1:600,000 Carte No. X (by Fr. Ganshof, J. Maury) (Folder 36F)
    - Historical map of southern Limbourg. 1:400,000, 686 (Folder 36F)
      Photostats and reduction, uncolored photostat.
    - (Untitled base map- photostat), 709. (Folder 36F)
  - Czechoslovakia
    - Tcheco-Slovaquie. G.S.G.S. 2758 1/M (Folder 36G)
    - S.G.A. 27.3.19 (Folder 36G)
      Boundaries proposed.
    - Carte d'ensemble des existences de charbon dans I'Etat Tschecho-Slovac. Cracovie 1919. (Folder 36G)
    - Les Pays Tscheques. (subdivisions) (Folder 36G)
      Photostat.
    - Le Duche de Cieszyn (Teschen) Silesie (Czech Poland) (Folder 36G)
    - (Sketch of Bohemia, on transparent paper) (Folder 36G)
  - France
    - A.G.S. base, 1:6,000,000 (Folder 36H)
      No key to information added to map.
    - France, 1:3,700,000 Departments, 63 (Folder 36H)
      Drawing on tracing linen, from base in Stieler's Atlas, sheet 26; and photostat.
    - France 1:3,000,000, 570 (Folder 36H)
      On tracing linen; no legend.
    - Paris, 1652 (photostat) (Folder 36H)
    - Paris sous Philippe Auguste 1:80,000 (Folder 36H)
    - Sketch map of motor roads around Paris. Geogr. Section, Peace Congress, No. 16. 1:63,360 (2 copies) (Folder 36H)
  - Alsace-Lorraine
    - A.G.S. base of Lorraine, 1:500,000, 25a (Folder 36I)
    - A.G.S. base of Alsace, 1:500,000, 7a (Folder 36I)
    - A.G.S. base Block Diagram, Lorraine (small), 25 (Folder 36I)
    - A.G.S. base Map, Alsace-Lorraine (from Geogr. Rev., Vol. VI, No.2, 1918; historical boundaries added) (2 copies), 647 (Folder 36I)
    - Alsace-Lorraine, percent speaking German (colored photostat), 616 (Folder 36I)
    - Alsace-Lorraine, (outline map), 616a (Folder 36I)
  - Greece
    - Greece- subdivisions. 681, 682, 683 (Box 36J)
      Photostat reduction of War Office map of Europe "Sofiya", "Istanbul" "Athenai".
    - Greek claims. (On photostat reduction of A.G.S.base, and also on section of A.G.S. base map of Europe, 1:3,000,000), 727 (Box 36J)
    - (Photostat reduction of A.G.S. base), 626 (Box 36J)
    - Hellenism in the Near East - ethnological map compiled by General Soteriades. 1:2,155,000 (photostat reduction), 780 (Box 36J)
    - From Carta Etnico-Linguistica del Oriente Europeo. Agostini. (photostat reduction; also plotted on A.G.S. base. 1/6M), 781, 1918 (Box 36J)
    - From South East Europe Ethnological Map. G.S.G.S. 3703a, 778, 1918 (Box 36J)
      Photostat reduction, plotted on A.G.S. base map. Attached to reverse side is a MS drawing on transparent paper, showing % of Armenians in Turkey. No. 614.
    - From G. Freytags Voelkerkarte von Europe. By A. Haberlandt, 779 (Box 36J)
      Photostat reduction, on A.G.S. base map.
  - Italy
    - A.G.S. base, Adriatic 1:6,000,000, 1a (Folder 36K)
    - (Part of A.G.S. base map of Europe, 1/3M, Adriatic, etc.), 625 (Folder 36K)
    - Comparison of Italy and California, 713 (Folder 36K)
      Drawing on linen.
    - Italy, 1:3,000,000;Population of cities, 572 (Folder 36K)
      Drawing and print.
    - A.G.S. base, 1:3,000,000, 58 (Folder 36K)
    - (Boundaries proposed; added to portion of I/M map of Europe by British War Office), 762 (Folder 36K)
    - Economic-linguistic map of Dec. 19, 1918, 583 (Folder 36K)
    - Important corridors of Central Alps (Trentino, etc.), 642b (Folder 36K)
      Also showing proposed frontiers; base being Europe 1/M, War Office.
    - Frontiers in the Tyrol. (Europe 1/M base, War Office) Dr. Johnson, 667 (Folder 36K)
    - PI. II, Distribution of population in Adije Basin, Trentino, 711 (Folder 36K)
    - PI. III, Adige Geographic unit (Folder 36K)
    - PI .V, Parallel system of east-west valley trenches or corridors and intervening mountain barriers, 720 (Folder 36K)
    - (Trentino-linguistic and frontiers, on War Office base), 753 (Folder 36K)
    - (Trentino - colored to show regions of Upper Adige and Trentino), 754 (Folder 36K)
    - A.G.S. Block Diagram. Trentino, 52a (Folder 36K)
    - A.G.S. Base, Tyrol. 1:1,000,000, 43a (Folder 36K)
    - (Tyrol - new frontiers), 656 (Folder 36K)
    - Fiume 1:20,800 Wagner and Debes (photostat), 775a (Folder 36K)
    - Trade of Fiume, 1910. Quantities - Destination, 775b (Folder 36K)
    - Trade of Fiume, 1910. Quantities - Source, 775b (Folder 36K)
    - Trade of Fiume, 1913. Imports, values, 765a (Folder 36K)
    - Trade of Fiume, 1913. Exports, values, 765b (Folder 36K)
    - Trade of Fiume, 1913. Imports, quantities, 766a (Folder 36K)
    - Trade of Fiume, 1913. Exports, quantities, 766b (Folder 36K)
    - (Untitled MS drawing of area covering Trentino, Trieste, etc., showing railways and political sub-divisions), 606a (Folder 36K)
    - Julian Venetia, 774 (Folder 36K)
      Portion of War Office map, showing proposed boundaries and linguistic line.
    - Istria -XXI, Linguistic boundaries of 1900 & 1910, 751 (Folder 36K)
    - Istria -XXII (Racial areas), 752 (Folder 36K)
    - Istria -Gorz & Gradisca, 583 (Folder 36K)
      Colored photostat, showing languages.
    - Les Nationalites en Istrie… Editions Bossard (Folder 36K)
    - VI, Relation of proposed boundaries to uninhabited areas. Istria, etc., 736 (Folder 36K)
    - VII, Density of Population (Istria), 737 (Folder 36K)
    - VIII Railways, and proposed boundaries, 738 (Folder 36K)
    - IV, Administrative divisions, called Cercles. lstria, 734 (Folder 36K)
    - IX, Roman period, 739 (Folder 36K)
    - X, 1101 period, 740 (Folder 36K)
    - X1, 1300-1500 period Approx. boundaries, 741 (Folder 36K)
    - XII, 1522-1797 period Approx., 742 (Folder 36K)
    - XIII 1647-1717 period County of Gradisca, 743 (Folder 36K)
    - XIV, Napoleonic, 744 (Folder 36K)
    - XV, Proposals of 1915, 745 (Folder 36K)
    - XVII Population of 1880, arranged by Judicial Districts, 747 (Folder 36K)
    - XVIII Population of 1890, arranged by judicial Districts, 748 (Folder 36K)
    - XIX Population in 1900 (Istria) by Judicial District, 749 (Folder 36K)
    - XX Population in 1910 (Istria) by Judicial District, 750 (Folder 36K)
    - A.G.S. Block diagram, Triest-Isonzo region (2 copies), 53 (Folder 36K)
    - (Untitled sketch of Triest-Isonzo region and Photostat), 606 (Folder 36K)
    - Areas and population of Dalmation Islands in 1900 (2 copies), 584a (Folder 36K)
    - Numbers speaking various languages in Dalmatian Islands, 675 (Folder 36K)
    - Suggested boundaries between Italy and Jugoslays, 714 (Folder 36K)
    - Austrian Adriatic - linguistic districts, 608a (Folder 36K)
    - Austrian Adriatic - portion of A.G.S. base, colored to show political units, 733 (Folder 36K)
    - (Portion of War Office sheet N.K.33, marked to show area and population inaccurate), 584 (Folder 36K)
    - (Assembled War Office sheets, labled Triest NL33, marked to show areas and population of Dalmation Islands, 1900 census), 584a (Folder 36K)
    - Part of A.G.S. base map of Austria-Hungary, marked to show London Line, proposed line, and linguistic line of Trentino, Istria & Dalmation Islands, 732 (Folder 36K)
    - Photostat of Triest sheet, War Office, showing proposed and London Lines (Folder 36K)
    - Photostat of Triest sheet, War Office, showing Austrian Adriatic linguistic distribution, 608 (Folder 36K)
    - Photostat of French chart 3564, Canal Maltemps, 1916 (Folder 36K)
    - Photostat of French chart 3667, Port of Sebenico, 1916 (Folder 36K)
  - Rumania
    - Population density and language. De Martonne. 1/M, 519 (Folder 36L)
      Hand colored & drawn; photostat of the same. Also original base on drawing linen.
    - A.G.S. base, 1/2M. (with boundary added, according to Treaty of Bucharest, May 7, 1918), 33a (Folder 36L)
    - (Part of A.G.S. base, with linguistic boundary), 660 (Folder 36L)
    - Territory taken from Rumania by Austria and Bulgaria, according to Treaty of Bucharest, May 7, 1918, 535 (Folder 36L)
    - The Dobrudja, 649 (Folder 36L)
    - The Dobrudja Boundary, 542, 1918 May (Folder 36L)
    - Rumania, Southwestern, language districts bordering on Yugoslavia (Folder 36L)
  - Russia
    - A.G.S. base. Russian Empire. 1:28,000,000, 36a (Folder 36O)
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000, 567 (Folder 36O)
      Colored to show population.
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000 (Folder 36O)
      Marked to show iron, coal, manganese & oil.
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000, 541 (Folder 36O)
      Railways added in ink.
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000 Siberia 1/10,000,000, 37a (Folder 36O)
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000 Siberia 1/3,000,000, 62 (Folder 36O)
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000 Siberia 1/6,000,000, 35a (Folder 36O)
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000 Siberia 1/6,000,000, 34 (Folder 36O)
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000 Siberia 1/3,000,000 (2 sheets), 64 (Folder 36O)
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000 Siberia, 631 (Folder 36O)
      Portion covering Black Sea area.
    - A.G.S. base. 1/3,000,000 Caucasia, 44a (Folder 36O)
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000 Caucasus (Folder 36O)
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000, 501 (Folder 36O)
      Photostat reduction, showing languages.
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000, 502 (Folder 36O)
      Photostat reduction, showing religions.
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000, 503 (Folder 36O)
      Photostat reduction, showing illiteracy.
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000 Baltic Basin (large and small sizes), 18a & 19 (Folder 36O)
    - A.G.S. base 1/3,000,000 Baltic Provinces 1:2,000,000, 19a (Folder 36O)
    - Russia (outline), 494 (Folder 36O)
    - Russia (outline)1:2,000,000 (2 sheets), 507 (Folder 36O)
    - Brest-Litovsk line (on tracing paper), 497 (Folder 36O)